Register of the Polish Subject Collection, 1918-2014
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials
  - Periodicals - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 97: 6--8)
    Newsweek, Angora, Wysokie Obcasy, Polityka, Forum, Wprost, Viva!, Gala, Zycie na Goraco, Przeglad, Claudia, Naj
  - Newspapers - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 98: 1)
    Zycie Warszawy, Rzeczpospolita, Gazeta Wyborcza
  - Periodicals - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 99: 1)
    Newsweek, Paris Match, Bunte, Time, L'Express,
  - Periodicals - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 99: 2)
    Wiadomosci KAI, Wojska Ladowe, Przekroj,
  - Publications - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - Periodicals - Benedict XVI, 2005 (Box-folder 99: 4)
    Przekroj, Newsweek, U.S.News
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1988 (Box-folder 99: 5)
    On Gogol Boulevard - Exlusive Reports on Poland
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2005 (Box-folder 99: 6)
    Wprost - Polska - Rosja
  - Miscellaneous newspapers - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 100: 1)
    Death of John Paul II, and election of Pope Benedict XVI
  - Miscellaneous newspapers - John Paul II, 2005 (Box-folder 101: 1)
  - PZPR - Internal Publications, 1980 (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - PZPR - Internal Publications, 1981 (Box-folder 102: 2)
  - PZPR - Internal Publications, 1982 (Box-folder 102: 3--5)
    Prawda o Polskiej Kontrrewolucji, NSZZ "Solidarnosc" wobec kryzysu gospodarki, Od grudnia do grudnia - Bilans dokonan w okresie stanu wojennego
  - PZPR - Internal Publications, 1983 (Box-folder 102: 6)
    Zeszyty dokumentacji politycznej, XIII Plenum KC PZPR
  - PZPR - Internal Publications, 1984-85 (Box-folder 102: 7)
    Zeszyty dokumentacji politycznej, Koncepcje programowe podziemia politycznego.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 103: 1)
    Biuletyn. Wydawany przez KW PZPR w Toruniu
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1977 (Box-folder 103: 2)
    Sprawozdanie na XVI Konferencje Sprawozdawczo-Wyborcza 1977 PZPR.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1979 (Box-folder 103: 3)
    Informator prawniczy dowodcy z zakresu prawa karnego i przepisow wykonawczych
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1971 (Box-folder 103: 4)
    Wytyczne Episkopatu Polski
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1988 (Box-folder 103: 5)
    Wydarzenia marcowe 1968r. Geneza, przebieg, nastepstwa.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1984 (Box-folder 103: 6)
    Informujemy. Wydzial Organizacyjny ZG ZSMP
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1988 (Box-folder 103: 7)
    Wytyczne w sprawie poznawania i analizowania nastrojow w Ochotniczych Hufcach Pracy.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1987 (Box-folder 103: 8)
    Problem tzw. Mniejszosci niemieckiej w Polsce Ludowej.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 103: 9)
    Wybory Samorzadowe
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 103: 10)
    Platforma dla Warszawy 2006-2010. Program samorzadowy Platformy Obywatelskiej
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 103: 11)
    Zeszyt Historyczny nr 11(dodatek "Newsweek"), "Wprost i Kultura"
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 103: 12)
    Jozef Gorski "Na przelomie dziejow" - 2 books
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1987 (Box-folder 104: 1)
    Pope John Paul II in the American Press
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2005 (Box-folder 104: 2)
    "Newsweek" nr 16 i nr 19
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 104: 3)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers, 2005 (Box-folder 104: 4)
    Los Angeles Time, San Jose Mercury News (JP II and Benedict XVI)
  - Boxes 105-109
    Boxes 105-109, are part of the Władysław Chojnacki collection and are listed at the end of the finding aid.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 1)
    Pamphlets, Posters (Ruch 10 kwietnia)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 2)
    Flyers, Pamphlets (Wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 3)
    Flyers, Pamphlets (Wybory Prezydenckie)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 4)
    Pamphlets, Posters, local newspapers (wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 5)
    Fyers, Poster, (Wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    Election Legislation, Lists of candidates (Wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2010 (Box-folder 111: 1)
    Election Legislation, Pamphlets, Banners (Wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2004 (Box-folder 111: 2)
    European Parliament
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2007 (Box-folder 111: 3)
    Flyers, Pamphlets, Posters,( Wybory Samorzadowe)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2007 (Box-folder 111: 4)
    Election Legislation, Lists of candidates, local newspapers (Wybory Samorzadowe).
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2002 - 2004 (Box-folder 112: 1--2)
    European Union - Pamphlets, Flyers, Posters.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 112: 3)
    J. Oleksy tapes transcript.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2007 (Box-folder 112: 4)
    Rydzyk tapes transcript. + CD
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2006 (Box-folder 112: 5)
    IX Zjazd Zwiazku Polakow na Litwie - projekt.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2002 (Box-folder 112: 6)
    Radio Free Europe - Polish Section.
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 2007 (Box-folder 112: 7)
    Twarze Katowickiej Bezpieki
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1971 (Box-folder 112: 8)
    Antoni Gorczewski /Zarys zycia i dzialnosci politycznej w szeregach KPP/.
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 1)
    Flyers - PiS
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 2)
    Flyers - Platforma Obywatelska
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 3)
    Flyers - PSL
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 4)
    Flyers - SLD
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 5)
    Miscellaneous flyers and posters
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 6)
  - Parliamentary Elections - Publications, 2014 (Box-folder 113: 7)
    Newspapers
  - Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box-folder 113: 8)
    The Lilpop sisters and their passions - CD
  - Miscellaneous, 2007 (Box-folder 113: 9)
    Santa Rosa Camp for women and children - CD (1939-1940)
  - Miscellaneous, 1918-1945 (Box-folder 113: 10)
    Two-headed Dragon. Story of the Mid-war Period in Upper Silesia. CD
  - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box-folder 113: 11)
    Two flyers. (Zawodowy Zwiazek Federacyjny, Wolnosc i Pokoj)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box-folder 113: 12)
    Stanislaw Tyminski. Flyer
  - Cassettes and CDs (Box-folder 114:)
  - An Unknown Odyssey of Polish Jews, undated (Box-folder 114: 1)
  - The Legacy of Jedwabne, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 114: 2)
  - Bitwa o Warszawe '44, undated (Box-folder 114: 3)
    Discovery Channel
  - Eurowybory 2009 (Box-folder 114: 4)
  - Legiony i poczatki wojska II Rzeczypospolitej, undated (Box-folder 114: 5)
    Polish and English Version
  - Ostatni Polkownik czyli sprawiedliwi., 1968 (Box-folder 114: 6)
    doc.
  - Bayer Full - PSL, undated (Box-folder 114: 7)
    music
  - 14 cassettes - concerts, independent radio broadcasts, Adam Michnik at Hoover, etc., 1956-1999 (Box-folder 114: 8)
  - VHS (Box-folder 115:)
  - The Journey to America, 1995 (Box-folder 115: 1)
    The Pilgrimage of Pope John Paul II to the United States
  - "Bomba w samolocie", "Katastrofa w Dorval", undated (Box-folder 115: 2)
  - "Nocna zmiana". Odwolanie Rzadu Olszewskiego. Czerwiec 1992 (Box-folder 115: 3)
  - Burning Questions, 1999 (Box-folder 115: 4)
    The story of Christian Poles in the Holocaust
  - Ojciec sw. na Podhalu, 1997 (Box-folder 115: 5)
  - Powodz. Historia katastrofy., 1997 (Box-folder 115: 6)
  - Ostatni "polkownik" czyli sprawiedliwi, 1968 (Box-folder 115: 7)
  - Rescued from Death in Siberia, 2001 (Box-folder 115: 8)
  - Interview with Edward Z. Mroz., 1994 (Box-folder 115: 9)
  - Walczymy z powodzia. Hoover Institution Archives, 2008 (Box-folder 115: 10)
  - V Pielgrzymka Papieza do Polski, 1995 (Box-folder 115: 11)
  - C.O.P. Hoover Institution Archives, 1980 (Box-folder 115: 12)
- Władysław Chojnacki collection, 1944-1953
  Biographical note
  Władysław Chojnacki was born on June 22nd, 1920 in Warsaw. He was best known as a notable historian, bibliographer, and an author of various books, articles, and conspiratorial publications. During World War II he attended the secret Uniwersytet Ziem Zachodnich (Uniwersytet Poznański), where he also received his doctorate in 1951. Additionally, he was actively involved as an officer in the Polish National Armed Forces.
  In 1953 he was working as a librarian at the Instytut Historii Polskiej Akademii Nauk, and later, in 1965, became the head of the department of Bibliografii Retrospektywnej XIX i XX wieku (Retrospective Bibliography of 19th and 20th century). He was awarded the Gold Cross of Merit in 1960, for his service to country and society. Chojnacki went on to receive his habilitation in 1967 from the Uniwersytet Wrocławski.
  Władysław Chojnacki contributed extensively to the Polish Collections at Hoover Archives: he was a major supplier of Polish independent publications between 1976 and 1990, helping the archives build the most complete collection outside of Poland.
  Władysław Chojnacki died on July 2nd, 1991
  Scope and Contents
  The Chojnacki collection is composed of World War II era Polish underground publications. Materials represent mostly the anti-Soviet and anti-communist underground between 1944 and 1953, both in Poland-proper and in the Soviet-occupied Eastern Poland. The vast majority of these imprints are in Polish, with a few in Ukrainian. Additionally, the collection includes the publications of the Warsaw Uprising of August to September, 1944.
  - Anti-Soviet and Anti-Communist underground materials, 1944-1953
    These materials represent mostly the anti-Soviet and anti-communist underground during 1944-1953, both in Poland-proper and in the Soviet-occupied Eastern Poland. The great majority of these imprints are in Polish, with a few in Ukrainian
    - Political Brochures A-C, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 1)
    - Political Brochures D-F, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 2)
    - Political Brochures G-I, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 3)
    - Political Brochures J-L, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 4)
    - Political Brochures M-N, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 5)
    - Political Brochures O, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 6)
    - Political Brochures P, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 7)
    - Political Brochures R, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 8)
    - Political Brochures S-U, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 9)
    - Political Brochures W, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 10)
    - Political Brochures W, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 11)
    - Political Brochures Z, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 54: 12)
      Two booklets in Russian; Collection of photographs of press clippings
    - Political Flyers A, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - Political Flyers B, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - Political Flyers C-D, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 3)
    - Political Flyers D, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 4)
    - Political Flyers E-I, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 5)
    - Political Flyers J-K, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 6)
    - Political Flyers L-M, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 7)
    - Political Flyers N, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 8)
    - Political Flyers O, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 9)
    - Political Flyers O, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 10)
    - Political Flyers P, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 11)
    - Political Flyers P, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 12)
    - Political Flyers Polacy, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 13)
    - Political Flyers Polacy, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 55: 14)
    - Political Flyers R, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - Political Flyers S-T, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - Political Flyers U, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - Political Flyers W, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - Political Flyers Z, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - Periodicals - Agencja Prasowa, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - Periodicals - Agencja Prasowa, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 56: 7)
    - Periodicals - A (Others), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - Periodicals - Antybolszewik, 1953 (Box-folder 56: 9)
      Agencja Spoleczno-Polityczna
    - Periodicals - ASP, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 56: 10)
      Alarm, Agencja Informacyjna, Agencja Rownosc, Agencja Bialostocka
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 56: 11)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny dla Duchowienstwa, 1945 (Box-folder 56: 12)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjno-Ideowy, 1944 (Box-folder 56: 13)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny Opracowany na Podstawie Audycji Stacji Zachodnich, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 56: 14)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny Ziemi Bialostockiej, 1945 (Box-folder 56: 15)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Kresowy, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 56: 16)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Prasy, 1945 (Box-folder 56: 17)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Radia Brytyjskiego, 1945 (Box-folder 56: 18)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Wewnetrzny, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Wewnetrzny Kresowiakow, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - Periodicals - Biuro Informacji Polskich, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - Periodicals - Bojownik, 1948 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - Periodicals - Bomba, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - Periodicals - Cele Rewolucji (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - Periodicals - Codzienne Wiadomosci, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 7)
    - Periodicals - Co Slychac, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 8)
    - Periodicals - Czarne na Bialym, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 9)
    - Periodicals - Czyn, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 57: 10)
    - Periodicals - Dawnym Szlakiem, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 11)
    - Periodicals - Dokumenty Chwili, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 57: 12)
    - Periodicals - Do Potegi Polski, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 13)
    - Periodicals - Drogowskaz, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 14)
    - Periodicals - Dzien Polski, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 15)
    - Periodicals - Dziennik Radiowy, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 16)
    - Periodicals - Echa Lesne, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 57: 17)
    - Periodicals - Echo, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 18)
    - Periodicals - Echo Baltyckie, 1947 (Box-folder 57: 19)
    - Periodicals - Echo Lubelskie, 1944 (Box-folder 57: 20)
    - Periodicals - Ekspres Podolski, 1945 (Box-folder 57: 21)
    - Periodicals - Gazeta Malopolska, 1944 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - Periodicals - Gazetka dla Wszystkich, 1948 (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - Periodicals - Gazetka Scienna A.K., 1945 (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - Periodicals - Glos, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - Periodicals - Glos Jednosci Polskiej, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - Periodicals - Glos Opozycji, 1946 (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - Periodicals - Glos o Wolnosc, 1948 (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - Periodicals - Glos Podziemi, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 8)
    - Periodicals - Glos Podziemia, 1947 (Box-folder 58: 9)
    - Periodicals - Glos Polski, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 10)
    - Periodicals - Glos Prawdy, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 11)
    - Periodicals - Glos Prawdy Polskiej, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 12)
    - Periodicals - Glos Robotniczy, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 13)
    - Periodicals - Glos spod Ziemi, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 14)
    - Periodicals - Glos Wolnosci, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 15)
    - Periodicals - Glos Wolny, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 16)
    - Periodicals - Glos Wsi, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 17)
    - Periodicals - Glos Ziemi Bialostockiej, 1944 (Box-folder 58: 18)
    - Periodicals - Glos z nad Narwi, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 58: 19)
    - Periodicals - Glos z Podziemia, 1947 (Box-folder 58: 20)
    - Periodicals - Honor I Ojczyzna, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 58: 21)
    - Periodicals - Informacja Lwowska, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 58: 22)
    - Periodicals - Informacje Polityczne, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 23)
    - Periodicals - Informacje Polskie, 1944 (Box-folder 58: 24)
    - Periodicals - Informator, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 58: 25)
    - Periodicals - Informator Podolski, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 26)
    - Periodicals - Informator Wsi, 1946 (Box-folder 58: 27)
    - Periodicals - Iskierki, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 28)
    - Periodicals - Iskra, 1945 (Box-folder 58: 29)
    - Periodicals - Jednosc, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - Periodicals - Jestem Polakiem, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 2)
    - Periodicals - Knieja, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 3)
    - Periodicals - Komitet Inicjatyw Spolecznych (K.I.S.), 1945 (Box-folder 59: 4)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Codzienny, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Informacyjno-Instruktazowy, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 7)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Informacyjny, 1947 (Box-folder 59: 8)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Polityczny, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 9)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Prasowy, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 10)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Radiowy, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 11)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Specjalny, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 12)
    - Periodicals - Konspekt Propagandowy, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 13)
    - Periodicals - Kraj, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 14)
    - Periodicals - Kresowy Komunikat, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 15)
    - Periodicals - Kresowy Zew, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 16)
    - Periodicals - Krotkie Wiadomosci Zolnierskie, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 17)
    - Periodicals - Kruszymy Kajdany, 1946 (Box-folder 59: 18)
    - Periodicals - Ku Wolnosci, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 59: 19)
    - Periodicals - Ku Zwyciestwu, 1946 (Box-folder 59: 20)
    - Periodicals - Lubelska Agencja Informacyjna, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 21)
    - Periodicals - Lubelski Biuletyn Radiowy, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 22)
    - Periodicals - Lubelskie Wiadomosci Codzienne, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 23)
    - Periodicals - Materialy dla Terenu, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 24)
    - Periodicals - Mazowiecki Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 25)
    - Periodicals - Miecz Chrobrego, 1944 (Box-folder 59: 26)
    - Periodicals - Mloda Polska, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 59: 27)
    - Periodicals - Mlody Ludowiec (Box-folder 59: 28)
    - Periodicals - Monitor Bialostocki, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 59: 29)
    - Periodicals - Mysl Polska, 1946 (Box-folder 59: 30)
    - Periodicals - Mysl Niezalezna, 1945 (Box-folder 59: 31)
    - Periodicals - Naboj, 1944 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - Periodicals - Na Czasie, 1944 (Box-folder 60: 2)
    - Periodicals - Na Posterunku, 1944 (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - Periodicals - Narodowiec, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - Periodicals - Narodowy Ruch Antybolszewicki, Undated (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - Periodicals - Narod Mowi, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - Periodicals - Narod w Walce, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - Periodicals - Na Strazy, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - Periodicals - Nasza Sprawa, 1946 (Box-folder 60: 9)
    - Periodicals - Nasz Biuletyn, 1946 (Box-folder 60: 10)
    - Periodicals - Nasz Czyn, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 11)
    - Periodicals - Niepodleglosc, 1946 (Box-folder 60: 12)
    - Periodicals - Nowe Informacje Polskie, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 13)
    - Periodicals - Nowiny, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 14)
    - Periodicals - Nowy Zew, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 15)
    - Periodicals - Nurt, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 16)
    - Periodicals - O Demokratyczna Polske, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 17)
    - Periodicals - Ogniwo, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 60: 18)
    - Periodicals - Okregowy Biuletyn Wenetrzny, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 19)
    - Periodicals - Orzel Bialy, 1946 (Box-folder 60: 20)
    - Periodicals - Ostatnie Wiadomosci, 1945 (Box-folder 60: 21)
    - Periodicals - Patria, 1946 (Box-folder 61: 1)
    - Periodicals - Plomien, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 61: 2)
    - Periodicals - Pobudka (Box-folder 61: 3)
    - Periodicals - Pochodnia Zwyciestwa, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 4)
    - Periodicals - Podziemne Informacje Radiowe P.I.R., 1945 (Box-folder 61: 5)
    - Periodicals - Pogadanka Zolnierska, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 6)
    - Periodicals - Polak, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 7)
    - Periodicals - Polonia, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 8)
    - Periodicals - Polowka, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - Periodicals - Polska, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 10)
    - Periodicals - Polska Informacja Polityczna, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 11)
    - Periodicals - Polska Informacja Tygodniowa, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 12)
    - Periodicals - Polska I Swiat, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 13)
    - Periodicals - Polska Niezalezna, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 14)
    - Periodicals - Polska Niezawisla, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 15)
    - Periodicals - Polska Solidarna, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 16)
    - Periodicals - Polska Walczaca, 1946 (Box-folder 61: 17)
    - Periodicals - Polska Walczy, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 61: 18)
    - Periodicals - Polskie Slowo, 1946 (Box-folder 61: 19)
    - Periodicals - Prawda, 1944 (Box-folder 61: 20)
    - Periodicals - Przedswit, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 61: 21)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad, 1944 (Box-folder 61: 22)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Polityczny, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 61: 23)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Prasowy, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 61: 24)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Wewnetrznej Sytuacji Politycznej, 1946 (Box-folder 61: 25)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Wydarzen, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 61: 26)
    - Periodicals - Puszcza Szumi, 1946 (Box-folder 61: 27)
    - Periodicals - Reduta, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 61: 28)
    - Periodicals - Rzeczpospolita Polska, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 29)
    - Periodicals - Serwis Specjalny Inki, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 30)
    - Periodicals - Sfinx, 1948 (Box-folder 61: 31)
    - Periodicals - Slowo Polskie, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 61: 32)
    - Periodicals - Sluzba Publiczna, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 33)
    - Periodicals - Sluzba Radiowa, 1944 (Box-folder 61: 34)
    - Periodicals - Sojusznik, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 35)
    - Periodicals - Sprawy Polskie, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 36)
    - Periodicals - Sprawy Polskie w Swiecie, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 37)
    - Periodicals - Straznica Kresowa, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - Periodicals - Straznica Podziemi, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 2)
    - Periodicals - Straznica Sumienia, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 3)
    - Periodicals - Sygnal, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 4)
    - Periodicals - Szydlo, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 5)
    - Periodicals - Tu Mowi Londyn, 1944 (Box-folder 62: 6)
    - Periodicals - Tygodnik, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 7)
    - Periodicals - Uwagi Na Czasie, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 8)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1940 (Box-folder 62: 9)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1944 (Box-folder 62: 10)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 11)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 12)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 13)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 14)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 15)
    - Periodicals - Untitled, 1946 (Box-folder 62: 16)
    - Periodicals - Walka, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 62: 17)
    - Periodicals - Walka, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 18)
    - Periodicals - Walka Narodu, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 62: 19)
    - Periodicals - Walka Swiatopogladowa, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 20)
    - Periodicals - Warszawa Niepodlegla, 1945 (Box-folder 62: 21)
    - Periodicals - Wesoly Posterunek (Box-folder 62: 22)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Biezace, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Informacyjne, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 2)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Londynu, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 3)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Londynu, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 4)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Radiowe, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 63: 5)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Radiowe I Informator, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 6)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Radiowe Polaka, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 7)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Robotnicze-Czestochowa, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 8)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Robotniczo-Chlopskie, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 9)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Tygodniowe, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 10)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Z Dnia, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 11)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci ze Swiata, 1951 (Box-folder 63: 12)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci z Frontow, 1944 (Box-folder 63: 13)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Zolnierskie, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 14)